[

](https://cidilabs.com/)

Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Cidi Labs, LLC (“Cidi Labs”) is committed to protecting your privacy and developing a website that gives you a useful and informative online experience. This Privacy Policy applies to our websites and related support services and governs data collection and usage. By using the Cidi Labs website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Please note that Cidi Labs’ Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) products are governed by separate SaaS agreements.

### Collection of Your Personal Information

Cidi Labs collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, employer name, or telephone number. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Cidi Labs. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. This information is used by Cidi Labs for the operation of the website and its services, to maintain quality, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Cidi Labs website. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through or on the Cidi Labs website, this information may be collected and used by others.

Cidi Labs encourages you to review the privacy policies and/or statements of websites you choose to link to from Cidi Labs, if any, so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. Cidi Labs is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or statements or other content on websites outside of the Cidi Labs websites.

For example, If you choose to use certain Cidi Labs services like our sandbox accounts by allowing the Learning Management System access to your information – you agree that use of your information by the LMS will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of that LMS.

### Use of Your Personal Information

Cidi Labs collects and uses your personal information to operate the Cidi Labs website and deliver certain items and/or services you have requested. Cidi Labs may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Cidi Labs and its affiliates.

​

Cidi Labs does not sell, rent, or lease your information or its customer lists to third parties. Cidi Labs may share data with trusted partners to help us perform business activities such as statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Cidi Labs, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. Cidi Labs does not use or disclose sensitive personal information without your explicit consent.

Cidi Labs keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Cidi Labs, in order to determine what Cidi Labs services are the most popular.

​

Cidi Labs will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Cidi Labs or the website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Cidi Labs; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Cidi Labs, or the public.

### Use of Cookies

The Cidi Labs website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Cidi Labs pages, or register with Cidi Labs’ website or services, a cookie helps Cidi Labs to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information. When you return to the same Cidi Labs website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Cidi Labs features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Cidi Labs services or websites you visit.

### Security of Your Personal Information

Cidi Labs secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Cidi Labs secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When personal information is transmitted to other websites, if at all, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Changes to This Statement

Cidi Labs will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. Cidi Labs encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Cidi Labs is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

Cidi Labs welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or believe that Cidi Labs has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact Cidi Labs via email at info@cidilabs.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

#### Contact

* [13894 S. Bangerter Parkway  
    Suite 200  
    Draper, UT 84020](https://goo.gl/maps/1hJxnw8dCemfgFmS8)

#### PRODUCTS

#### Company

© 2023 Cidi Labs, LLC All Rights Reserved

#### CIDI LABS NEWSLETTER

Name
----

### Position

Description
